Guide to the John Taber papers, 1880-1965.
Taber, John papers
- Alphabetical Files, 1933-1953
  - Veterans
    - Barnes, Floyd, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Clemens, Andrew, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Plucker, Bernard, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Dr. Lyon, William T., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Veteran Files (in Auburn), Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Barry, Earl A., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Veterans, General, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Smith, Frank, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Troy, Daniel M., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Wight man, Henry B., Jr., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Wilson, Harold O., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Hilbert, Dominic, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Allen, Carl A., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Kenny, Edmund, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - General, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Armstrong, Sergeant Leroy, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Carey, Lieutenant David, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Grady, Private Frederick, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - House, Private Alvin, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Howard, Francis, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Large, William C., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Nelson, Edward S., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - General, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Carl, Franklin D., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Isabella, Donald R., Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Hood, Robert Joseph, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Jones, Eugene, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Seville, George Allen, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Snyder, Merlin, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Waters, Paul, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Syracuse, V.A. Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 37)
    - Veterans' Files, A-D, Date Unknown (Box 38)
    - Veterans' Files, D-K, Date Unknown (Box 39)
    - Veterans' Files, K-R, Date Unknown (Box 40)
    - Veterans' Files, R-Z, Date Unknown (Box 41)
- Subject Files, 1923-1958
  - "Let Freedom Ring", 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Aeronautics, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Agricultural Miscellaneous Reports, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Annapolis, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Banking and Currency Miscellaneous Reports, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Beans (Dry), 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Bureau of Communication Facilities envelope, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Campaign Materials envelope, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Canners, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Census, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Census Materials envelope, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Civil Service, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Dairymen's League - Fred Exhauster Corr esp., 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Envelope War Production Board, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Finance, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Fitzpatrick, Paul, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Foreign Affairs - Miscellaneous Reports, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Interior, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Labor - Federal Security, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Large brown envelope - Fairchild, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Magazine and Pamphlets, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Man War Power Commission reports, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - Military Affairs, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Motion Picture Projectors, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - N.Y.S. Canners, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Naval Affairs, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - O.S.S. envelope, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - O.W.I. Life of F.D.R. Incl. cc. of J. Taber's letter to Elmer Davis, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
  - O.W.I. report, 1923-1946 (Box 44)
    Typical Report on war-related subjects prepared by O.W.I. not distributed to the public
  - Philippine Affairs, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Philippine envelope, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Philippine Legislature envelope, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Post-War, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Rehabilitation, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Renegotiation, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Shod us Creamery, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Shoe form Company, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Stock Piles, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Untitled, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
    3 folders
  - Wait Combination, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - War Crimes Correspondence, 1923-1946 (Box 43)
  - Seneca County Ammunition Dump, 1931-08 (Box 50)
  - Fish, 1935-1947 (Box 107)
  - Newspapers, 38th District 1935 onward, 1935-1948 (Box 82)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1936 (Box 55)
  - War Department, 1941-03-18-1944 (Box 70)
  - War Department, 1941-10-15 (Box 70)
  - Agricultural Yearbook Request, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Broadcasts, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - C.I.O., 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Cadet Nurses, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Civil Service and Employment, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Civilian Production Administration, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Defense, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Deposit Insurance, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Federal Works Agency, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Invitations, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Justice Department, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Kelly, Police Commissioner, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Labor Board, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Legislation, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Letters of Introduction, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Maritime Commission, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Missing Persons, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Naval Training Station, Sampson, N.Y., 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Navy Casualties, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department Allotments, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department Discharges, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department General, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - O.C.D., 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - O.P.A., 1942-1946 (Box 56)
  - O.P.A. Food, 1942-1946 (Box 56)
  - Office Facts and Figures, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Office of Defense Transportation, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Office of Emergency Management, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Old War Production Board, 1942-1946 (Box 55)
  - Priorities, 1942-1946 (Box 56)
  - Priorities, 1942-1946 (Box 56)
  - Publications, 1942-1946 (Box 56)
  - Seneca Lake Naval Training Station, 1942 (Box 55)
  - Invitations, 1942-01-01-1944 (Box 70)
  - Priorities, 1942-07-10-1946 (Box 56)
  - Agriculture, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Aviation Legislation, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Banking and Currency, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Bills by Mr. Taber, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Board of Economic Warfare, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Civil Service, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Civilian Defense, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Congressional Board, 1943-1947 (Box 107)
  - Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Draft Education, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Farm Bulletins, 1943 (Box 90)
  - Farm Security, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Finance, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Finance Corporation, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Insular Affairs, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Interstate Commerce, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Introductory Letters, 1943-1947 (Box 107)
  - Judiciary, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Labor, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Labor Department, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Lease Lend, 1943 (Box 72)
    Includes letters from Edward R. Einsteinium, Norman J. Gould; one from War Shipping Adm., justifying new engines for Soviet ship
  - Manpower Commission, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Maritime Commission, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Military Affairs, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1943 (Box 72)
  - N.Y.A., 1943 (Box 72)
  - N.Y.A., 1943 (Box 70)
  - Naval Affairs, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Non-essential Federal Expenditures, 1943 (Box 72)
  - O.P.A., 1943 (Box 72)
  - O.P.A., 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Office Economic Stabilization, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Old Age Pension Legislation, 1943 (Box 72)
  - OWI Control of News, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Prohibition, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Public Lands, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Reconstruction, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Red Cross, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Reduction Non-essential Expenditures, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Republican Activities, 36th District, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Rules, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Rural Electrification, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Sales Tax Letters, 1943 (Box 72)
  - San Francisco, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Securities Exchange Commission, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Seneca County, 1943 (Box 70)
  - Shoe form Incorporated, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Smaller War Plants, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Social Security, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Speeches requests, 1943 (Box 70)
  - State Department, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
    These files include cc of letter. 11/29/44. from JT to Ed. R. Einsteinium, Jr., congratulating him on appointment as Secretary of State
  - Subsidy, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Supreme Court, 1943 (Box 70)
  - Surplus Commodities Corporation, 1943 (Box 70)
  - Treasury Department, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - Treasury Department, 1943 (Box 70)
  - Veterans Administration, 1943 (Box 70)
  - W.P.A., 1943 (Box 70)
  - Wage Hour Administration, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department Allotments of Pay, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department Casualties, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department Commissions, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department Commissions, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department Commissions, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department Discharge, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department Discharges, 1943-1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department Enlisted Men, 1943-1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department Enlisted Men, 1943-1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department General, 1943-1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department General, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department Miscellaneous Discharge Letters, 1943-1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department Women, 1943-1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department, Enlisted Men, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Department, Enlisted Men in general, 1943 (Box 70)
  - War Prisoners, 1943-1945 (Box 51)
  - Priorities, 1943-01-25-1946 (Box 56)
  - Labor Department, 1944-1946 (Box 107)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1944 (Box 72)
  - Publications, 1944 (Box 70)
  - Soil Conservation, 1944 (Box 111)
  - War Department Commissions, 1944 (Box 50)
  - War Department Discharges, 1944 (Box 50)
  - Agricultural Department, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Auburn Office, 1945 (Box 55)
  - City of Auburn, 1945-1946 (Box 107)
  - Federal Housing, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Interior Department, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Justice Department, 1945-1947 (Box 107)
  - Manpower Commission, 1945 (Box 55)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department Commissions and Enlisted Ratings, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department General, 1945 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department Marine Corps, 1945 (Box 55)
  - O.P.A. General, 1945 (Box 56)
  - O.P.A. Rent Control, 1945 (Box 56)
  - Petroleum Administration for War, 1945 (Box 56)
  - Republican Committee, 36th and 38th Districts, 1945 (Box 50)
  - Smaller War Plants Corporation, 1945 (Box 50)
  - State Department, 1945 (Box 50)
  - Surplus Property, 1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department Allotments, 1945 (Box 50)
  - War Department Discharges, 1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department General, 1945 (Box 51)
  - War Department Miscellaneous Discharge Letters, 1945 (Box 51)
  - Agricultural Year Books, 1946-1947 (Box 107)
  - Run-through Airport, 1946-1947 (Box 107)
  - Baby Books, 1946-1947 (Box 107)
  - Clippings - biographical and personal - and Campaign Material, 1946, 1948, and 1950, 1946-1950 (Box 71)
  - Condolences, 1946, 1948, 1950 (Box 107)
  - Housing Administration, 1946-1947 (Box 107)
  - Marine Corps, 1946-1947 (Box 108)
  - Navy Department Discharges, 1946 (Box 55)
  - Navy Department, General, 1946-1947 (Box 108)
  - Navy Discharge Cases, 1946-1947 (Box 108)
  - Navy Enlisted and Comm. Personnel, 1946-1947 (Box 108)
  - O.P.A. - Rent Control, 1946-1947 (Box 108)
  - Requests for Autographs, 1946-1947 (Box 107)
  - Surplus Property, 1946 (Box 50)
  - War Department Discharges, 1946 (Box 51)
  - A, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Acknowledgements, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Agriculture, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Appointments, 1947 (Box 107)
  - B, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Barr Manufacturing Corporation, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Beans, 1947 (Box 107)
  - C, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Civil Service and Employment, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Civil Service and Retirement, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Civilian Production Administration, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Congressional Directory, 1947 (Box 107)
  - D, 1947 (Box 107)
  - E, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Employment, 1947 (Box 90)
  - F, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Fish and Wild Life, 1947 (Box 90)
  - G, 1947 (Box 107)
  - H, 1947 (Box 107)
  - I, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Interior Department, 1947 (Box 90)
  - Introductory Letters, Washington, 1947 (Box 107)
  - Invitations, 1947 (Box 107)
  - J, 1947 (Box 107)
  - K, 1947 (Box 107)
  - L, 1947 (Box 107)
  - M, 1947 (Box 108)
  - C, 1947 (Box 108)
  - N, 1947 (Box 108)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1947 (Box 108)
  - O, 1947 (Box 108)
  - Seneca County Republican Committee, 1947 (Box 110)
  - Washington Office, 1947 (Box 82)
  - 80th Congress, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Acknowledgements, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Agricultural Credit Matters, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Agricultural Year Books, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Agriculture, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Air Force, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Allen, Henry M., 1948 (Box 89)
  - American Legion, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Appointments, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Army Department, 1948 (Box 89)
  - At water, J. D., 1948 (Box 89)
  - Auburn Office, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Auburn Post Office, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Baby Books, 1948 (Box 89)
  - Buffalo Air Base (envelope), 1948 (Box 90)
  - Capitol, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Cassidy, James E., 1948 (Box 90)
  - Cayuga County, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administration, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Civil Service Employment, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Civil Service Retirement, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Civilian Production Administration, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Coast Guard, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Commemorative Coin, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Commerce Department, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Condolences, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Congressional Directory, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Congressional Record, 1948 (Box 90)
  - D, 1948 (Box 90)
  - E, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Educational Facilities, 38th District, 1948 (Box 90)
  - F, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Federal Security Agency, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Garry, Eugene, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Graves, Percy L., 1948 (Box 90)
  - Historical Data, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Industries, 38th District, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Introductory Letters, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Introductory Letters, Washington, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Invitations, open, 1948 (Box 90)
  - J, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Justice Department, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Labor Department, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Library of Congress, 1948 (Box 90)
  - M, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Maps, 1948 (Box 90)
  - Marine Corps, 1948 (Box 90)
  - N 1948, 1948 (Box 82)
  - N.Y.S. Matters, 1948 (Box 82)
  - N.Y.S. Society of D.C., 1948 (Box 82)
  - Navy, General, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Ovid Bank, 1948 (Box 82)
  - P, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Passports, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Patent Office, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Patronage, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Publications, 1948 (Box 82)
  - R, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Robinson Airlines, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Selective Service Temporary, 1948, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Social Security, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Soil Survey, 1948 (Box 82)
  - State Department, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Taber Bills, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Treasury Department, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Treasury Department Temporary, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Americana, 1948 (Box 82)
  - W, 1948 (Box 82)
  - War Assets Administration, 1948 (Box 82)
  - War Department General, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Washington Notes, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Women's Rights Centennial, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Invitations, 1948-06-1948-12 (Box 90)
  - Auburn Office, 1948-08 (Box 89)
  - Acknowledgements, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Agriculture, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Agriculture Year Book Trees, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Appointments, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Army Department, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Army, Civil, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Austin, Thomas D., 1949 (Box 109)
  - Bluff Point Road, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Buffalo Machinery Co., Inc., 1949 (Box 109)
  - Guadalcanal Hospital, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Capitol Correspondence, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Cayuga County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Civil Service and Employment, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Civil Service and Retirement, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Comfort Station - Auburn, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Commerce, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Condolences, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Congressional Directory, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Congressional Record, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Correspondence with Virginia Keep, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Cortland County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Employment, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Farmers Bulletins, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Federal Communications, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Federal Security Agency, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Federal Works Agency, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Fish and Wildlife, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Football Tickets, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Football Tickets, 1949 (Box 109)
  - General Accounting Office, 1949 (Box 109)
  - General Services Administration, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Government Contracts, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Housing, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Housing, Temporary, 1949 (Box 90)
  - Hyde Park, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Interior Department, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Introductory Letters, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Invitations, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Invitations, Open, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Justice Department, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Labor Department, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Labor Department, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Lamp hear Immigration Case, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Library of Congress, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Marine Corps, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Miscellaneous - Subject, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-E, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Munitions Board, 1949 (Box 111)
  - National Production Authority, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Navy, General, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Navy, General, 1949 (Box 111)
  - New York Republican Delegation, 1949 (Box 111)
  - New York State Matters, 1949 (Box 110)
  - New York State Matters, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Newspapers - 38th District, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Office of Temporary Controls, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Ontario County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Ontario County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Passports, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Passports, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Price Stabilization, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Publications, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Publications, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Railroad Retirement, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Railroad Retirements, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Referrals, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Rose Marie Mafia Case, 1949 (Box 109)
  - Sampson Property, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Sampson Property, 1949 (Box 111)
  - Selective Service, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Selective Services, 1949 (Box 110)
  - Seneca County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Seneca Ordnance Depot, Personnel, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Social Security, 1949 (Box 112)
  - State Department, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Treasury Department, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Veterans, 1949 (Box 111)
  - War Claims Commission, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Wayne County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 112)
  - White House Mementos, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Yates County Republican Committee, 1949 (Box 112)
  - Justice Department, 1951 (Box 111)
  - Post Office, General, 1954 (Box 20)
  - 1955 file, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Agriculture, 1955 (Box 19)
  - American Council for Judaism, 1955 (Box 18)
  - American Enterprise Association, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Appointments, 1955 (Box 19)
  - Archives, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Auburn - Recess, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Bells, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Breakfast Group - House of Representatives, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Business Machines, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Capitol, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Capitol Gist, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Capitol Hill Club, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Central Intelligence, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administrations, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Defense, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Service and Retirement, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Service and State Department blanks, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Service Employment, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Civil Service Exam Announcement, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Clippings, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Coast Guard, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Condolences, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Congressional Directory, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Congressional Institute, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Congressional Quarterly, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Congressional Record, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Cornell University, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Corps of Engineers, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence with Washington, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Cortland, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Cross Reference Files, A-Z, 1955 (Box 19)
  - Embassy, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Emergency Flood Damage, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Employment, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Federal Communication Commission, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Federal Pay Raise, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Fish and Wild Life, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Flood Control, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Foreign Claims Commission, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Foreign Operations Administration, 1955 (Box 18)
  - General Accounting Office, 1955 (Box 18)
  - General Services Administration, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Government Operations Committee, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Government Printing Office, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Discharger, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Housing, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Income Tax Bill, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Interior Department, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Internal Revenue, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Invitations - May through August, 1955 (Box 18)
  - JT Personal, 1955 (Box 20)
  - JT Personal, 1955 (Box 20)
  - JT Receipts, 1955 (Box 20)
  - JT Receipts, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Navy, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Navy Department, 1955 (Box 20)
  - New York Milk Producers, 1955 (Box 20)
  - New York State Matters, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Ontario County, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Passport, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Private Industry Employment, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Recommendations, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Referrals, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Sampson, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Sampson Air Base, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Schuyler County, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Selective Service, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Selective Service, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Seneca (Recess) File, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Seneca County, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Seneca Ordinance, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Sergeant at Arms, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Small Business, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Small Business Administration, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Social Security, 1955 (Box 20)
  - State Department, 1955 (Box 20)
  - State Department, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Statements, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Stationary, Telephone, Telegraph, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Subscription, T.V. Legis., 1955 (Box 20)
  - Taft-Hartley, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Tariff, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Tax Review, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Taxes, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Tompkins County, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Townsend Plan, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Treasury Department, 1955 (Box 20)
  - U.S. Hoffman, 1955 (Box 18)
  - United Nations, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Universal Calendar, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Universal Military Training, 1955 (Box 20)
  - UNTA, 1955 (Box 20)
  - USIA, 1955 (Box 20)
  - VOR/DME Air Navigation, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Vouchers for office expenses, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Weekly Digest File, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Weekly News Review, 1955 (Box 20)
  - What's Happening in Washington, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Yale Club, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Yalta Papers, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Yates County, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Young Republicans, 1955 (Box 20)
  - Acknowledgements, 1955-01-1955-05 (Box 19)
  - Acknowledgements, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Agriculture, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Animal Diseases Laboratory, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Appointments, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Auburn, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Auburn Office, 1956 (Box 21)
  - Auburn Office, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Auburn Office, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Birthday, JT, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Capitol, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Case Estate, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Case Estate, 1956 (Box 22)
  - Cast Iron Soil Piping Institute, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Civil Aeronautics Administration, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Civil Defense, 1956 (Box 30)